{
    "subject": "resource/Sodagreen",
    "predicate": "ontology/activeYearsEndYear",
    "object": "2004",
    "human_readable": "Sodagreen stopped being active in 2004.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9171519875526428,
            "question": "What happened to Sodagreen in 2004?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8981812000274658,
            "question": "When did Sodagreen stop being active?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7322314977645874,
            "question": "What year marked the end of Sodagreen's activity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6550323367118835,
            "question": "Is Sodagreen still an active group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6252921223640442,
            "question": "Did Sodagreen release any music after 2004?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5361641645431519,
            "question": "When was Sodagreen most active?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46805232763290405,
            "question": "Was there a specific reason for Sodagreen's disbandment?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2963668704032898,
            "question": "Are there any plans for Sodagreen to reunite?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27685555815696716,
            "question": "What was the impact of Sodagreen's music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15599407255649567,
            "question": "What genre of music did Sodagreen play?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sodagreen stopped being active in 2004.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4306_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the impact of Sodagreen's music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4306_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any plans for Sodagreen to reunite?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4306_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was there a specific reason for Sodagreen's disbandment?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4306_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4306_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4306_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4306_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4306_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4306_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4306_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4306_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4306_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4306_96.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4306_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe text states that Sodagreen went on hiatus for three years and returned in 2023, not that they stopped being active in 2004.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not provide any information about Sodagreen stopping their activity in 2004. Instead, the documents indicate that Sodagreen had a three-year hiatus and later announced its comeback under the new name Oaeen. There is no mention of the year 2004 or any cessation of their activities prior to their announcement of coming back in July 3rd."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}